Guide to the Oppenheimer collection of theater programs, 1906-1999 MS 489
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Oppenheimer collection of theater programs
1906-1999 (bulk 1950-1999)
1950-1999
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Oppenheimer, Ed
MS 489
2 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
A collection of theater programs mainly from Houston, Texas, but also including New York, London, Dallas, and Fort Worth, collected by Ed Oppenheimer.
2 lin. ft. (2 boxes)
Biographical Note
The city of Houston has been a home to theater almost since its founding, with the first professional production on June 11, 1838. Since then, the Houston Theater District has grown until it seats the second largest number of people in the country, behind only New York. In 1951, "Houston was the site…of The Playhouse, the first permanent building built in America specifically to be a theatre-in-the-round" (Dauphin, 83). Another historic venue is the Alley Theatre whose growth mirrors that of Houston theater, evolving from one simple room to hosting two main stages holding 824 and 310 seats. Productions at the Alley tended to be popular, modern plays early on, and it was only later that they leaned towards the classics. Other venues today include the "national AIA prize-winning Jesse H. Jones Hall for the Performing Arts" (Holmes 2), the Miller Outdoor Theatre, and the Hobby Center for the Performing Arts. The Hobby Center is home to Theatre Under The Stars, the "largest non-profit producer of musical theater in America" (About).
Houstonian Ed Oppenheimer collected these programs from the 1900s to the 1990s from various theaters in Houston as well as New York, London, Dallas, and Fort Worth.
Scope and Contents
A collection of theater programs mainly from Houston, Texas, but also including New York, London, Dallas, and Fort Worth, collected by Ed Oppenheimer.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
From Edward Oppenheimer, Jr. on January 24, 2000, 438 play programs from 1906-1999.
Index Terms
Subjects
Theater
Document Types
playbills; programs (documents)
Subjects (Corporations)
Alley Theatre (Houston, Tex.)
- Series I: New York theater season programs, 1906-1913; 60648
  - "Oh!Oh! Delphine," Knickerbocker Theater, 1912-10; 60653 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Broadway Jones," George M. Cohans's Theater, 1912-10; 60652 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "La Traviata," Metropolitan Opera House, undated.; 60651 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Under Many Flags," New York Hippodrome, 1912-1913; 60650 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Series II: Houston theater season programs, 1960-1999; 60287
  - "Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo", Music Hall, 1968-1969; 1960-03; 60646 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Fiddler on the Roof," Jones Hall, 1968-1969.; 60643 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Billy Liar," Alley Theatre, 1969-02-13-1969-03-30; 60642 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "War and Peace," Alley Theatre, 1969-04-03-1969-05-04; 60641 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "All the Way Home," Alley Theatre, 1969-06-12-1969-07-13; 60640 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "The Rose Tattoo," Alley Theatre, 1969-10-16-1969-11-16; 60639 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Tartuffe," Alley Theatre, 1970-01-04-1970-12-04; 60638 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Everything in the Garden," Alley Theatre, 1969-11-02; 60637 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Saint Joan," Alley Theatre, 1969-01-09-1969-02-09; 60636 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Dames at Sea," The New Hungry I Theatre, 1969-07-15; 60635 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "The Star Spangled Girl," Holiday Dinner Theatre, 1969-04; 60634 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Any Wednesday," Windmill Dinner Theatre, 1969-06-12-1969-07-13; 60633 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "The World of Carl Sandburg," Alley Theatre, 1970-04-21-1970-06-07; 60630 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "The Andersonville Trial," Alley Theatre, 1970-01-22-1970-02-22; 60629 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Dear Liar," Alley Theatre, 1970-02-05-1970-03-29; 60628 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Blithe Spirit," Alley Theatre, 1970-04-30-1970-05-31; 60627 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Dear Love," Alley Theatre, 1970-09-17-1970-09-27; 60626 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Our Town," Alley Theatre, 1971-02-25-1971-03-28; 60625 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Ring Round the Bathtub," Alley Theatre, 1971-01-03-1971-12-03; 60624 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail," Alley Theatre, 1971-01-14-1971-02-14; 60623 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie," Alley Theatre, 1970-04-08-1970-05-09; 60622 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Dial 'M' for Murder," Alley Theatre, 1971-05-20-1971-06-20; 60621 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Mourning Becomes Electra," Alley Theatre, 1971-10-22-1971-11-22; 60620 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Camino Real," Alley Theatre, 1971-10-21-1971-11-21; 60619 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "No, No, Nanette," Jones Hall, 1971-10-24-1971-10-29; 60618 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "1776," Jones Hall, 1970-10-28-1970-11-01; 60617 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Fiddler on the Roof," The Windmill Dinner Theatre, 1972-04-25-1972-05-28; 60614 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "The Taming of the Shrew," Alley Theatre, 1972-04-13-1972-05-14; 60613 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Last of the Red Hot Lovers," The Windmill Dinner Theatre, 1972-03-21-1972-04-22; 60612 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Hadrian VII," Alley Theatre, 1972-03-02-1972-04-02; 60611 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Spoon River," Alley Theatre, January 20-February 20, 1972.; 60610 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "A Flea in Her Ear," Alley Theatre, 1972-01-09-1972-12-02; 60609 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Pantagleize," Alley Theatre, 1972-10-19-1972-11-19; 60608 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Mame," Houston Music Theatre, 1972-07-04-1972-07-16; 60607 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Child's Play," Alley Theatre, 1972-05-25-1972-06-25; 60606 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Life With Father," Alley Theatre, 1972-11-30-1973-01-07; 60603 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Colette," Alley Theatre, 1973-03-01-1973-04-01; 60602 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "The School for Wives," Alley Theatre, 1973-04-12-1973-05-13; 60601 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Jacques Brel," Alley Theatre, 1973-05-24-1973-06-01; 60600 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Inherit the Wind," Alley Theatre, October 18-November 18, 1973.; 60599 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Beginner's Luck!," Dean Goss' Dinner Theatre, 1973-11; 60598 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Swan Lake," The National Ballet of Canada, 1973-03-06-1973-03-11; 60597 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Gaslight," The Windmill Dinner Theatre, 1973-07-31-1973-09-02; 60594 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Ah, Wilderness," Alley Theatre, 1973-11-29-1974-01-06; 60593 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "A Midsummer Night's Dream, Alley Theatre, 1974-01-17-1974-02-17; 60592 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Count Dracula," Alley Theatre, 1974-04-11-1974-05-12; 60591 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "The Decline and Fall of the Entire World as Seen Through the Eyes of Cole Porter," Alley Theatre, 1974-05-23-1974-06-23; 60590 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Coppelia," Houston Ballet, 1974-10-31-1974-11-02; 60589 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Wilson," Alley Theatre, 1974-10-17-1974-11-17; 60588 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Oklahoma," Miller Theatre, 1973-06-28-1973-07-07; 60587 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner," Alley Theatre, 1974-11-28-1975-01-05; 60586 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Twelfth Night," Alley Theatre, 1975-01-16-1975-02-16; 60583 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Pippin," Music Hall, 1975-02-15-1975-02-16; 60582 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire," Alley Theatre, 1975-02-27-1975-03-30; 60581 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Tobacco Road," Alley Theatre, 1975-04-10-1975-05-11; 60580 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "The Contest," Alley Theatre, 1975-05-22-1975-06-22; 60579 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Indians," Alley Theatre, 1975-10-23-1975-11-23; 60578 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Puttin' on the Ritz," Million Dollar City Dump, 1975.; 60577 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Little Me," Music Hall, 1975-12-31-1976-01-04; 60576 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Cabaret," Cabaret Theatre, 1976.; 60573 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Dames at Sea," Cabaret Theatre, 1976.; 60572 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Juno and the Paycock," Alley Theatre, 1976-03-11-1976-04-11; 60571 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Show Off," Alley Theatre, 1976-04-22-1976-05-30; 60570 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Pajama Game," Theatre Under the Stars at Miller Outdoor Theatre, 1976-06-17-1976-06-29; 60569 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Company," Cabaret Theatre, 1976.; 60568 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Gigi," Theatre Under the Stars at Miller's Theatre, 1976.; 60567 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Front Page," Alley Theatre, 1976-01-11-1976-12-04; 60566 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Sty of the Blind Pig," Alley Theatre, 1976-10-21-1976-11-28; 60565 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia," Alley Theatre, 1976-01-22-1976-02-29; 60564 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "My Fair Lady," Cabaret Theatre, 1976.; 60563 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "You Never Can Tell," Alley Theatre, 1976-12-09-1977-01-16; 60562 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Corn is Green," Alley Theatre, 1977-01-27-1977-02-27; 60559 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "The Shadow Box," Alley Theatre, 1977-03-09-1977-04-09; 60558 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "The Runner Stumbles," Alley Theatre, 1977-03-10-1977-04-10; 60557 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "The Ritz," Cabaret Theatre, 1977-01; 60556 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "How the Other Half Love," Alley Theatre, 1977-04-21-1977-05-29; 60555 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Variety of programs, Dallas Music Hall at Fair Park, 1977 season.; 60554 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Echelon," Alley Theatre, 1978-01-25-1978-02-26; 60551 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "The Happy Time," Alley Theatre, 1978-12-07-1979-01-21; 60550 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas," Tower Theatre, 1978.; 60549 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Mary Stuart," Alley Theatre, 1978-10-20-1978-11-27; 60548 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "The Importance of Being Earnest," Alley Theatre, 1978-12-08-1979-01-15; 60547 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Scream," Alley Theatre, 1978-10-19-1978-11-26; 60546 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "The Royal Ballet," Jones Hall, 1978-06-06-1978-06-11; 60545 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Don Juan in Hell," Alley Theatre, 1979-03-15-1979-04-15; 60542 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Black Coffee," Alley Theatre, 1979-12-06-1980-01-20; 60541 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Artichoke," Alley Theatre, 1979-02-01-1979-03-04; 60540 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Side by Side by Sondheim," Alley Theatre, 1979-04-26-1979-06-03; 60539 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "An Evening of Dance," Forth Worth Ballet, 1979.; 60538 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Liza Minelli in Concert," Jones Hall, 1979-06-12-1979-06-14; 60537 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Fiddler on the Roof," Miller Theatre, 1979-05-10-1979-05-19; 60536 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Indulgences in the Louisville Harem," Alley Theatre, 1979-10-18-1979-11-25; 60535 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "The Cherry Orchard," Alley Theatre, 1981-01-31-1981-03-02; 60532 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "The Gospel According to St. Matthew," Alley Theatre, 1981-03-1981-04; 60531 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Ten Little Indians," Alley Theatre, 1981-05-28-1981-06-28; 60530 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Oh Coward!," Alley Theatre, 1981-04-24-1981-06-01; 60529 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Cyrano de Bergerac," Alley Theatre, 1981-10-15-1981-11-15; 60528 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Brigadoon," Downtown Music Hall, 1981-10-29-1981-11-08; 60527 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "The House of Blue Leaves" Alley Theatre, 1981-12-03-1982-01-03; 60526 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "The Wall" Alley Theatre, 1982-04-15-1982-05-16; 60523 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "The Elephant Man" Alley Theatre, 1982-01-14-1982-02-14; 60522 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Way Upstream" and "Absent Friends," Alley Theatre, 1982-03-1982-04; 60521 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "The Red Bluegrass Western Flyer Show," Alley Theatre, 1982-11-26-1983-01-03; 60520 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "And If that Mockingbird Don't Sing" and "Paradise," Alley Theatre, 1982-02-1982-03; 60519 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Talley's Folly," Alley Theatre, 1982-05-27-1982-06-27; 60518 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Greater Tuna," Alley Theatre, 1982-07-29-1982-08-29; 60517 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Close Ties," Alley Theatre, 1982-10-14-1982-11; 60516 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Lena Horne: the Lady and Her Music," Jones Hall, 1983-03; 60515 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Sugar Babies," Music Hall, 1983-04; 60514 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Peter Pan," Music Hall, 1983.; 60513 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Zorba," Jones Hall, 1983-09; 60512 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "The Dresser," Alley Theatre, 1983-10-20-1983-11-20; 60511 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Gorey Stories," Main Street Theatre, 1983-12-16-1984-01-21; 60510 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Paint Your Wagon," Theatre Under the Stars in the Music Hall, 1984-10-24-1984-11-04; 60507 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Annie," Theatre Under the Stars in the Music Hall, 1984-12-20-1984-12-30; 60506 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Crimes of the Heart," Alley Theatre, 1984-03-08-1984-04-08; 60505 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Season's Greetings," Alley Theatre, 1984-11-29-1985-01-06; 60504 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Tarantara! Tarantara!," Main Street Theatre, 1984-12-14-1985-01-26; 60501 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Quartermaine's Terms," Alley Theatre, 1985-01-17-1985-02-17; 60500 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Sugar," Music Hall, 1985-02-20-1985-03-03; 60499 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Sweet Bird of Youth," Alley Theatre, 1985-02-28-1985-03-31; 60498 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "And a Nightingale Sang..." Alley Theatre, 1985-05-23-1985-06-23; 60497 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Cabin in the Sky," Music Hall, 1985-10-24-1985-11-04; 60496 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Kiss Me, Kate," Alley Theatre, 1985-11-21-1986-01-05; 60495 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Much Ado About Nothing," Alley Theatre, 1985-04-11-1985-05-12; 60494 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "On Golden Pond," Alley Theatre, 1985-03-05-1985-04-05; 60493 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Betrayal," Alley Theatre, 1985-03-12-1985-04-12; 60492 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Greater Tuna," Tower Theatre, 1985.; 60491 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "A...My Name is Alice," Alley Theatre, 1985-06-20-1985-08-04; 60490 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Various performances, Stages, 1985.; 60489 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Execution of Justice," Alley Theatre, 1985-10-10-1985-11-10; 60488 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Kind Lady," Alley Theatre, 1985-07-18-1985-09-01; 60487 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "A Chorus Line," Music Hall, 1985.; 60486 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Trelawny of the Wells," Alley Theatre, 1986-11-27-1987-01-11; 60483 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Pack of Lies," Alley Theatre, 1986-02-27-1986-03-20; 60482 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Carousel," Music Hall, 1986.; 60481 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Foreigner," Alley Theatre, 1986-05-22-1986-06-22; 60480 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Ain't Misbehavin'," Music Hall, 1986.; 60479 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Spring Awakening," Alley Theatre, 1986-04-10-1986-05-11; 60478 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas," Tower Theatre, 1986-05; 60477 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Miss Firecracker Contest," Alley Theatre, 1986-01-16-1986-02-16; 60476 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "How the Other Half Lives," Alley Theatre, 1986-07-10-1986-08-31; 60475 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - " Another Part of the Forest," Alley Theatre, 1986-10-09-1986-11-09; 60474 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Leader of the Pack," Stages Repertory Theater, 1986-12-04-1986-12-28; 60473 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Immigrant: A Hamilton County Album," Alley Theatre, 1987-03-05-1987-04-05; 60470 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Glengarry Glen Ross," Alley Theatre, 1987-01-22-1987-02-22; 60469 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "The Common Pursuit," Alley Theatre, 1987-05-28-1987-06-28; 60468 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "A Lie of the Mind," Alley Theatre, 1987-04-16-1987-05-17; 60467 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Singin' in the Rain," Music Hall, 1987-02; 60466 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Cabaret," Jones Hall, 1987-08; 60465 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Shooting Stars," Alley Theatre, 1987-07-09-1987-08-30; 60464 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "My One and Only," Jones Hall, 1987-10; 60463 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Henceforward," Alley Theatre, 1987-10-08-1987-11-15; 60462 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Self Defense," Alley Theatre, 1987-10-22-1987-11-22; 60461 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Stepping Out," Alley Theatre, 1987-11-26-1988-01-03; 60460 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "The Miracle Worker," Alley Theatre, 1988-01-14-1988-02-14; 60457 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Big River Adventures of Huckleberry Finn," Jones Hall, 1988-06; 60456 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Odd Couple," Jones Hall, 1988-06; 60455 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "elvis: An American Musical," Jones Hall, 1988-07; 60454 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "South Pacific," Jones Hall, 1988-02; 60453 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Music Man," Jones Hall, 1988-08; 60452 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Dirty Linen," Rice Players, undated.; 60451 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Can-Can," Jones Hall, 1988.; 60450 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Road to Mecca," Alley Theatre, 1988-10-20-1988-11-20; 60449 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Merry Wives of Windsor," Alley Theatre, 1988-12-01-1989-01-01; 60448 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Lucky Spot,", 1988-02-25-1988-03-27; 60447 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "A Class 'C' Trial in Yokohama," Alley Theatre, 1988-04-07-1988-05-08; 60446 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Tom Foolery," Alley Theatre, 1988-06-09-1988-07-17; 60445 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Shear Madness: A Comedy Whodunit," Tower Theatre, 1989.; 60442 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "A View from the Bridge," Alley Theatre, 1989-01-12-1989-02-12; 60441 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Heaven's Hard," Alley Theatre, 1989-02-23-1989-03-26; 60440 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Me and My Girl," Jones Hall, 1989-02; 60439 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "The Waltz of the Toreadors," Alley Theatre, 1989-04-06-1989-05-07; 60438 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Steel Magnolias," Alley Theatre, 1989-05; 60437 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Les Miserables," Jones Hall, 1989-06; 60436 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Fiddler on the Roof," Jones Hall, 1989; 60435 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Measure for Measure," Alley Theatre, 1989-10-12-1989-11-12; 60434 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Nunsense," Jones Hall, 1989-11; 60433 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "A Christmas Carol," Alley Theatre, 1989-11-24-1989-12-31; 60432 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "The Music of Andrew Lloyd Webber," Jones Hall, 1990-11; 60431 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Shirley MacLaine," Music Hall, 1990-07; 60430 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Into the Woods," Jones Hall, 1989-02; 60429 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?," Alley Theatre, 1990-01-11-1990-02-11; 60428 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Private Lives," Alley Theatre, 1990-02-22-1990-03-22; 60427 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Starlight Express," Music Hall, 1990-04; 60426 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "A Chorus Line," Music Hall, 1990-04; 60425 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Three Sisters," Alley Theatre, 1990-04-05-1990-04-29; 60424 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "The Sunshine Boys," Jones Hall, 1990-06; 60423 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Jekyll and Hyde," Alley Theatre, 1990-05-24-1990-07-01; 60422 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Oklahoma!," Music Hall, 1990-09; 60421 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "The King Stag," Alley Theatre, 1990-09-01-1990-09-30; 60420 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "As You Like It," Alley Theatre, 1990-10-21-1990-11-18; 60419 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "The Wizard of Oz," Music Hall, 1990-12; 60418 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "A Tuna Christmas," The Grand 1894 Opera House, 1991; 60415 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Rumors: a Farce," Music Hall, 1991-01; 60414 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Joe Turners Come and Gone," Alley Theatre, 1991-01-06-1991-02-03; 60413 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Phantom," Music Hall, 1991-01-25-1991-02-10; 60412 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "M. Butterfly," Jones Hall, 1991-03; 60411 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Harvey," Alley Theatre, 1991-02-10-1991-03-10; 60410 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "West Side Story," Music Hall, 1991-03-05-1991-03-17; 60409 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Grand Hotel," Jones Hall, 1991-04; 60408 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Evita," Music Hall, 1991-04-09-1991-04-21; 60407 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Svengali," Alley Theatre, 1991-04; 60406 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Jerome Robbin's Broadway," Music Hall, 1991-06; 60405 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "The Merry Widow," Music Hall, 1991-10-01-1991-10-20; 60404 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "A Flea in Her Ear," Alley Theatre, 1991-10-17-1991-11-17; 60403 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Cinderella," Music Hall, 1991-12-07-1991-12-29; 60402 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Marriage Play," Alley Theatre, 1991-01-02-1991-02-02; 60399 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Chess," Music Hall, 1992-01-28-1992-02-16; 60398 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Paint Your Wagon," Music Hall, 1992-03-05-1992-03-22; 60397 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Miss Evers' Boys," Alley Theatre, 1992-02-13-1992-03-15; 60396 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "American Vaudeville," Alley Theatre, 1992-03-26-1992-04-26; 60395 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "La Cage Aux Folles," Music Hall, 1992-05-05-1992-05-24; 60394 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Forever Plaid," Alley Theatre, 1992-05; 60393 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Annie Warbucks," Music Hall, 1992-09-24-1992-10-11; 60392 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "The Front Page," Alley Theatre, 1992-09-10-1992-10-10; 60391 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Danton's Death," Alley Theatre, 1992-10-27-1992-11-15; 60390 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Here's Love," Music Hall, 1992-12-08-1992-12-27; 60389 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "The Foreigner," No theater listed, 1992.; 60388 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Hello, Dolly!," Music Hall, 1993-01-26-1993-02-14; 60385 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Lips Together, Teeth Apart," Alley Theatre, 1993-01-07-1993-02-07; 60384 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Our Town," Alley Theatre, 1993-02-18-1993-03-21; 60383 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Dracula: A Musical Nightmare," Alley Theatre, 1993-04-01-1993-05-02; 60382 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Brigadoon," Music Hall, 1993-03-16-1993-04-04; 60381 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Sayonara," Music Hall, 1993-04-25-1993-05-16; 60380 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Our Lady of the Tortilla," The Actor's Workshop, 1993-05-07-1993-05-23; 60379 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Macbeth," Alley Theatre, 1993-05-13-1993-06-13; 60378 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Crazy for You," Dallas Music Hall, 1993-05; 60377 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Cyrano de Bergerac," Alley Theatre, 1993-09-02-1993-10-10; 60376 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Fiddler on the Roof," Music Hall, 1993-09-21-1993-10-10; 60375 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Dancing at Lughnasa," Alley Theatre, 1993-10-21-1993-11-21; 60374 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Beauty and the Beast," Music Hall, 1993-11-17-1993-12-26; 60373 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "The Most Happy Fella," Music Hall, 1994-02-01-1994-02-20; 60370 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Tartuffe," Alley Theatre, 1994-02-24-1994-03-27; 60369 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Orpheus Descending," Alley Theatre, 1994-04-07-1994-05-08; 60368 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "South Pacific," Music Hall, 1994-04-05-1994-04-24; 60367 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Shakespeare For My Father," Alley Theatre, 1994-06-02-1994-07-03; 60366 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Mamet Oleanna," Alley Theatre, 1994-04; 60365 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Hot Mikado," Music Hall, 1994-05-10-1994-05-29; 60364 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Sound of Music," Music Hall, 1994-10-14-1994-10-30; 60363 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Crucible," Alley Theatre, 1994-11; 60362 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?," Hamman Hall Rice University, 1994-10-27-1994-10-29; 1994-11-03-1994-11-05; 60361 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Peter Pan," Music Hall, 1994-11-29-1994-12-18; 60360 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Three Tall Women," Alley Theatre, 1995-02-10-1995-03-11; 60355 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Arms and the Man," Alley Theatre, 1995-03-17-1995-04-15; 60354 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "The Mystery of Irma Vep," Alley Theatre, 1995-01-06-1995-02-04; 60353 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Angels in America Part 2: Perestroika," Alley Theatre, 1995-04; 60352 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Man of La Mancha," Music Hall, 1995-05-04-1995-05-21; 60351 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Follies," Music Hall, 1995-03-23-1995-04-09; 60350 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Angels in America Part 1: Millennium Approaches," Alley Theatre, 1995-04; 60349 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Jekyll and Hyde," Music Hall, 1995-01-20-1995-02-19; 60348 (Box 2, Folder 2)